eet Munjapara

J (+91)7283817858

Objective

As a frontend Developer With 2+ years of experience. I specialize in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React JS, and Next JS. Known for creative, organized work, driven by a passion for top-notch websites. Excel in collaboration, and embrace challenges for growth.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript.

Frameworks and Tools: React. JS, Next. JS(13, 14) Postman, Figma, Node. JS, Express, Git.

Database Management Systems: Non-Relational (MongoDB), Firebase

Others::REST API, HTML, CSS, tailwind CSS, Material UI, SCSS, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Redux Saga, Firebase, Next UI,

Zustand, Agile Methodology.

Experience

Albiorix Technology PVT LTD

Dec 2021 - July 2024 Software Engineer Ahmedabad

• MarketsEQ || Next.js 13

- * MarketsEQ is the layer between the product and the digital world. It acts as a liaison between consumer goods and customers, enhancing product experience and serving customers with a smart product assistant (OpenAI).
- * Implemented functionalities such as system prompts and the ability to upload audio and get transcripts with graphs. Also fixed bugs in the existing project.
- K-Chart || React.js
 - * Developed features for managing comprehensive Patient details, including patient information, disease, reports, and payments. Implemented patient CRUD operations, filters, pagination, and infinite scrolling.
 - * Analyzed design requirements and recommended technical solutions to ensure project scalability, maintainability, and efficiency. Followed Agile Software Development methodology throughout the project.
- Talent 500 Employer Management System || React.js
 - * Designed and developed multiple sections, including job and customer stepper forms, and implemented PDF download and preview functionality. Managed development tasks and bug fixes to enhance system performance.
 - * Created new common components and hooks, and integrated REST APIs with unit test cases to meet evolving requirements.

INEXTURE Solutions LLP

Apr 2021 – June 2021

Ahmedabad

Apprenticeship

- Made customer end basic website
- Worked on small features and bugs as an individual contributor, understood end-to-end flows of all the services
- Learned new techniques, and it's applications in industry life.

Projects

Todo Manager || React.js, TypeScript, ... || DEMO

Aug 2020 - Nov 2021

- Created a simple To-Do List Manager where users can add tasks, mark them as completed, and delete them. Users can view all tasks or filter them based on their completion status.
- Enabled users to add new tasks with descriptions and due dates, mark tasks as 'completed', and delete tasks.
- Implemented the ability to filter tasks by 'completed' or 'pending' status, improving user task management experience.

Online Towing System | Android, phpmyadmin

- Automated the vehicle towing process to improve efficiency for the traffic regulatory team and government.
- Developed an Android application for real-time management and tracking of towed vehicles.
- Integrated phpMyAdmin for database management to handle vehicle, owner, and violation records.

Education

B.Tech In Computer Science Engineering

NSIT, Ahmedabad Science Stream

Nov 2016 - May 2020

GPA: 7.86

June 2014 - March 2016

Sarthak Vidhyalay, Ahmedabad

Certifications

Akash Technology: Basic understanding of React and React Js

Coursera: Introduction to JavaScript